<FTL>

<eventList name = "GB_BALLISTIC_STORES"> <!--NOW UNUSED, HERE FOR REFERENCE-->
	<event load = "GB_STOREEVENT_OLD_FED_STORE_AUTOCANNONS"/>
	<event load = "GB_STOREEVENT_ASTEROID_AUTOCANNON_STORE"/>
	<event load = "GB_STOREEVENT_ALIEN_AUTOCANNONS"/>
	<event load = "GB_STOREEVENT_ENTHUSIAST_CANNONS"/>
	<event load = "GB_STOREEVENT_FED_AQUILA_STORE"/>
	<event load = "GB_STOREEVENT_SEPARATIST_NANO"/>
</eventList>

<eventList name = "GB_GENERIC_EVENTS">
	<event load = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED"/>
	<event load = "GB_MILITIA_ESCORT"/>
	<event load = "GB_FED_BOMBER_DISTRESS"/>
</eventList>

<eventList name = "GB_ITEMS">
	<event load = "GB_FED_RESEARCH_RAIL"/>
	<event load = "GB_MUSEUM_TOUR"/>
</eventList>

<event name = "GB_STOREEVENT_OLD_FED_STORE_AUTOCANNONS" unique = "true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_federation" global="false">
		<color r="215" g="255" b="200" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You expect to find a well stocked Federation market at this Merchant's beacon, but instead, there's only a small station and one singular patrol ship. Hopefully there is enough to stock up on for your journey here.</text>
	<ship load = "MU_GHOST_FED_BOMBER" hostile = "false"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Visit the store.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You meet a friendly face as you approach the store. "Welcome, welcome. I haven't seen many folks around here on my rotation at this here posting. I assume you're looking to trade?"</text>
			<store>STORE_STANDARD</store>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>You take notice of an old Federation vessel outfitted for transport duty docked at the station. Worth investigating?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Yep, that's my old girl. Fancy a bit of history? Me and the boys kept them in running shape since the war with the Mantis. Interested in buying something as old as she is?"</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Sure.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"These are living history lad, you know. Be careful with them."</text>
					<store>STORE_BALLISTIC_AUTOCANNON</store>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>We'd rather see some up to date weapons.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"If you insist. You're missing out, you know, these newfangled weapons just lack a certain something."</text>
					<store>STORE_STANDARD</store>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!-- <event name = "GB_OLD_ALLIANCE_STORE" unique = "true"/> PROBABLY THE BALLISTIC SHIP UNLOCK. ALSO UNFINISHED-->

<event name="GB_STOREEVENT_FED_AQUILA_STORE" unique="true"> <!--- trimmed version of the Deserter event -->
	<text>A market has set up operations on a side of a heavily modified decommissioned fleetship of old Federation make. Most likely one of the early batches of Aquila-class Battlecarriers that were common during the onset of the Federation-Mantis War; now sparsely sighted outside of planetary militias, Independents, and anyone else that might be interested in a well protected ship for long range hauls in the less fortunate systems. Worth taking a look?</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Request docking access.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Request received and granted, you are ready to enter and dock at landing pad... 5. Welcome to our humble store." Your ship approaches and docks at the designated internal landing pad where you disembark your ship and walk towards the store front.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Shop.</text>
				<event load="STORE_LOAD_GENERIC"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Inquire about the strange choice of venue.</text>
				<event>
				<text>The operator of this store front coughs to clear his throat. "This thing? Just a demilitarized Aquila. Converted for use as a long range hauler. Ample shields and firepower to keep any trigger happy Pirate off your back. Are you looking to trade, or are you just curious? We have some old hand-me-downs in surplus if you’re interested.”</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Nah, just access the regular store.</text>
						<event load="STORE_LOAD_GENERIC"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Sure, let's buy some of their old surplus.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You continue on to the old store.</text>
							<store>STORE_BALLISTIC_STANDARD_AUTOCANNON</store>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We don't need to go shopping right now.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Both you and the fleetship remain at this beacon while your FTL drive charges. </text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name = "GB_STOREEVENT_ASTEROID_AUTOCANNON_STORE" unique = "true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_federation" global="false">
		<color r="215" g="255" b="200" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You expected to see a large supply depot and patrols in this area, but to your surprise you initially couldn't find anything worth of note at this beacon, and started to charge the FTL drive until you've picked up a signal coming from a derelict vessel in a nearby thick asteroid belt. Worth taking a look?</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Head over into the asteroid belt and investigate.</text>
		<event>
			<environment type = "asteroid"/>
			<text>You are surprised to see a derelict outpost inside a crater of a dwarf planet within the asteroid field. As you approach for a landing they hail you on Federation channels. "Wasn't expecting a Federation vessel coming this way into our area of operations for another couple of months. We're short on munitions, and we're struggling to provide for the strikes this far deep in enemy territory with how infrequent supply runs have been. Perhaps we can come to an arrangement?"</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Hand over some ammunition to access a store. [-5 }]</text>
				<event>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="missiles" min="-5" max="-5"/>
					</item_modify>
					<store>STORE_STANDARD</store>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Enquire about the ammo dependency.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"These old things are running the foolproof classic load out of Autocannons and Bombs. Works perfectly fine up until you operate a bit further than a stone toss away from the supply lines. Hard getting supplies this far out without being overt in this enemy sector. You're more than free to take some off our hands in our inventory. No use keeping cannons that can't fire."</text>
					<choice>
                        <text>Agree to trade for a reduced cost. [-2 }]</text>
                        <event>
                            <item_modify>
                                <item type="missiles" min="-2" max="-2"/>
                            </item_modify>
                            <store>STORE_BALLISTIC_AUTOCANNON_BOMB_NO_AMMO</store>
                        </event>
                    </choice>
                    <choice>
                        <text>Let's stick to the regular store. [-5 }]</text>
                        <event>
                            <item_modify>
                                <item type="missiles" min="-5" max="-5"/>
                            </item_modify>
                            <store>STORE_STANDARD_NO_AMMO</store>
                        </event>
                    </choice>
                    <choice>
                        <text>We are not interested.</text>
                        <event>
                            <text>You are unable to help and apologise. You wish them luck and promise to send word of their situation the next time you come across a Federation contact. They are grateful, but you can't shake the feeling that it wasn't enough.</text>
                        </event>
                    </choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>If they're low on ammo than they are an easy target, attack!</text>
				<event>
					<text>As you begin to charge up your weapons, you detect a vessel coming in fast, must be one of the interdictors returning from their mission. You get ready for battle!</text>
					<ship load = "GB_FED_INTERDICTOR" hostile = "true"/>
					<choice>
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL_FIGHT"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Leave it.</text>
		<event>
			<text>We don't have time for a wild goose chase.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something on board the ship.</text>
				<event load = "STORAGE_CHECK_REAL"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_STOREEVENT_ALIEN_AUTOCANNONS" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_generic" global="false">
		<color r="215" g="255" b="200" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You find yourself surrounded by a variety of vessels of all sorts of shapes, colours, and markings. Some are more familiar and others are completely unknown to you. It appears that you have stumbled across a fair. Selling everything between knick-knacks to military grade equipment. There are a few merchants trying to attract your attention.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Trade with the Separatist.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"These guns: vital in defense against the [Harmony]. The Harmony: Harms many. These [guns] also harm many. I have many guns. Purchase or I shall [harm]."</text>
			<ship load="LIST_SHIPS_SEPARATIST_GENERIC" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Shop.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Separatist directs you over to their many wares.</text>
					<store>STORE_BALLISTIC_STANDARD_COILGUN</store>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Trade with the Federation veteran.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The highly decorated soldier attempts to instill you with Federation patriotism and fervor as he tries to convince you to buy surplus Autocannons, however you begin to doubt he even served at all when you notice his medals are crafted from tinfoil and bottlecaps.</text>
			<ship load="LIST_SHIPS_FED_GENERIC" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Shop.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The alleged veteran stands in attention and salutes as you browse the store.</text>
					<store>STORE_BALLISTIC_STANDARD_AUTOCANNON</store>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Trade with the Free Mantis.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Free Mantis chatters and trills excitedly at you. "Other traders, they don't like me. They think me a thief! But you are from Federation yes-yes? You come trade with me. Come see, I have thingies to sell!"</text>
			<ship load="LIST_SHIPS_FREEMANTIS_GENERIC" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Shop.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Engi very generous. I came to say hello to Federation Engi but he couldn't stay around. Gave me many things if I did not follow.  Want to see what they gave?"</text>
					<store>STORE_ENGI</store>
				</event>
				<event>
					<text>"I saw a Federation officer man not long ago! Must be very high rank for his ship is painted entirely orange! I had ran onboard when he docked and he screamed of joy when he saw me onboard with him! He gave me many things if I went back to where I come. Very generous Federation man. Want to see his gifts?</text>
					<store>STORE_REBEL</store>
				</event>
				<event>
					<text>"Zoltan left lots of thingies back at home. Many shiny but mostly junk. But here is some things Federation man might want!"</text>
					<store>STORE_ZOLTAN</store>
				</event>
				<event>
					<text>"Coalition, very strange. Act very big and tough. But when I come onboard there was only just a single slug! Now act very scared and gave me everything, was good tradings. Now you want trade? </text>
					<store>STORE_COALITION</store>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_STOREEVENT_ENTHUSIAST_CANNONS" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_generic" global="false">
		<color r="215" g="255" b="200" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>As soon as you jump in, you are immediately hailed repeatedly by the Miltiaman. "Guests! Come in and visit my brand new Ballistics Emporium! We sell Cannons! Missiles! And uh... other things, because no one buys the god damn Cannons and Missiles! But please, buy my Cannons!"</text>
	<ship load="GB_MILITIA_STATION" hostile="false"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Check out the emporium.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh good, oh good! Guests at last! Have you come to purchase an Autocannon? Perhaps a mint condition Leto? Oh please, my stock is expansive, endless even!"</text>
			<store>STORE_BALLISTIC_AUTOCANNON</store>
			<choice hidden="true" req="soldier">
				<text>(Soldier Crew) "Do you offer anything better?"</text>
				<event>
					<text>You expect the Militiaman to get offended, but instead she gets even more excited. "I found this not too long ago, but I have been reserving it for someone special. You're the first person to show any interest, so here you go!"</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Buy the prototype Autocannon.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"I hope you enjoy it!" The Militiaman dances with joy. You take a browse of the market as well on your way out.</text>
							<store>STORE_BALLISTIC_AUTOCANNON</store>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-65" max="-65"/>
							</item_modify>
							<weapon name="GB_ROTARY_AC"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Nevermind.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Militiaman's voice suddenly turns cold. "Head right, you'll find the general marketplace..." She storms off, her thunderous tears soak you as she goes by.</text>
							<store>STORE_BALLISTIC_AUTOCANNON</store>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Shop around.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack!</text>
		<event>
			<text>Why are so many people adamant on selling these things still? They won't for much longer if you have a say in it!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Ignore the emporium.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The station continues to target you with a slue of enthusiastic advertisements, but you simply fly away.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_STOREEVENT_SEPARATIST_NANO" unique="true">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_separatist" global="false">
		<color r="215" g="255" b="200" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>To your surprise there is indeed a Separatist ship here transmitting the trade beacon. Though it doesn't appear that anythings amiss as the Separatist ship simply drifts around silently near you. You attempt to hail but you do not hear anything besides the crackle of the radio communicator and a faint buzzing sound. Preliminary scans does not answer any questions either as the ship despite being fully functional and responsive is devoid of any lifesigns.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_SEPERATIST_NANOCLOUD" hostile="false" />
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attempt to salvage the ship</text>
		<event>
			<text>The mystery of what happened to the crew of this trader doesn't matter to you. The thoughts of what may be stowed onboard in its cargo holds and the riches that may be left inside is alluring... but before you can board the ship it begins taking defensive patterns and begins to power up its weapons!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Try to communicate and offer to trade.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You attempt to hail again but all you can pick up is the same buzzing sound. For no harm of trying you ask if its willing to trade.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue</text>
				<event>
					<text>You hear a faint buzzing sound in reply and your terminal recieves access to the Separatists digital kiosk to trade or buy from. It seems they're open for business.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>The ship opens a digital interface, and displays its wares for you to browse.</text>
							<store>STORE_BALLISTIC_STANDARD_COILGUN</store>
					</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_SLUG">
		<text>(Slug Crew) Try to detect life signs.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Slug tries to sense some form of intelligence aboard the enemy ship. They detect faint signs of potential life, but it's near impossible for them to tell.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Attempt to salvage the ship</text>
				<event>
				<text>The mystery of what happened to the crew of this trader doesn't matter to you. The thoughts of what may be stowed onboard in its cargo holds and the riches that may be left inside is alluring... but before you can board the ship it begins taking defensive patterns and begins to power up its weapons!</text>
					<ship hostile="true" />
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Ignore the ship.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You've lost interest in the mystery of what happened with the Separatist Trader, and prepare to move on.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event />
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="separatist"> <!-- I didn't finish this, I want this to be similar to the Crystal merchant event, where after communicating with your Separatist you are able to trade easily with the Merchant and have a random reward-->
		<text>(Separatist Crew) Ask your Separatist about the strange phenomena.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Separatist explains that the ship is indeed manned, it's just the Separatist had entered a nanoform, most likely as a precaution. They contact the vessel, and, recognising a friendly face, offer a small reward and open a store.</text>
			<autoReward level = "LOW">standard</autoReward>
			<store>STORE_BALLISTIC_STANDARD_COILGUN</store>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have no further desire to interact further with the strange ship.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED" unique="true">
   <text>You arrive to find what was once a supply caravan in a debris field; most likely victims of Pirates. There is no response to your hails.</text>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Dock with one of the transports and investigate.</text>
      <event load="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER" />
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Dock with one of the escorts and investigate.</text>
      <event load="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT" />
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true" req="GB_LIST_RECON_DRONES">
      <text>(Recon Drone) Use a Recon Drone to quickly investigate each ship.</text>
      <event load="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_RECON" />
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true" req="LIFE_SCANNER">
      <text>(Lifeform Scanner) Run a scan on the caravan to detect if there are any survivors.</text>
      <event load="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_SCAN" />
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Leave the caravan alone.</text>
      <event />
   </choice>
</event>

<eventList name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER">
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_GOOD"/>
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_BAD"/>
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_AUGMENT"/>
</eventList>

<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_GOOD">
   <text>It looks like the pirates or who ever attacked the caravan had already taken anything it was transporting or otherwise not bolted to the floor. You salvage what you can before leaving.</text>
   <autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Take time to investigate one of the Escorts.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Although it'll take more time, surely there is something left behind worth looking for.</text>
         <modifyPursuit amount="1" />
         <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Continue...</text>
            <event load="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_DELAYED" />
         </choice>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true" req="SCRAP_COLLECTOR">
      <text>(Scrap Recovery Arm) Attempt to recover additional salvage.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Your scrap recovery arm slowly gathers up any usable debris from the caravan wrecks drifting nearby.</text>
         <autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true" req="MAGNET_ARM">
      <text>(Magnetic Arm) Attempt to recover additional salvage.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Your Magnetic Arm makes quick work out of collecting the small space debris that floats around the wreckages.</text>
         <autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Leave.</text>
      <event />
   </choice>
</event>

<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_BAD">
	<text>It looks like the pirates or who ever attacked the caravan had already taken most of the goods carried by the Transport, however they were not the most thorough, and you find a reasonable amount of salvage.</text>
   <autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Take time to investigate one of the Escorts.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Although it'll take more time, surely there is something left behind worth looking for.</text>
         <modifyPursuit amount="1" />
         <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Continue...</text>
            <event load="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_DELAYED" />
         </choice>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Leave.</text>
      <event />
   </choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_AUGMENT">
   <text>Who ever attacked the caravan must've missed this Transporter or mysteriously wasn't interested in ransacking it for its contents. Regardless the crew is long dead and there is ample supplies to help you stock yourself for your mission.</text>
   <autoReward level="RANDOM">augment</autoReward>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Take time to investigate one of the Escorts.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Although it'll take more time, surely there is something left behind worth looking for.</text>
         <modifyPursuit amount="1" />
         <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Continue...</text>
            <event load="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_DELAYED" />
         </choice>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Leave.</text>
      <event />
   </choice>
</event>

<eventList name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT"> <!-- LIKE JESUS HOW MANY EVENT OUTCOMES-->
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_GOOD"/>
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_BAD"/>
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_CREW"/>
</eventList>

<event name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_GOOD">
   <text>The cause of the outcome of the engagement has been made clear once you boarded the vessel. It seems the escorts were still operating a few quaint Autocannons, and had ran out of ammunition during the fight. Upon examining the weapon, you discover it is still in functional order, albeit dry on ammunition, and is ready to be installed!</text>
   <autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
   <weapon name="GB_CARAVAN_REWARD" />
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Take time to investigate one of the Transports.</text>
      <event>
         <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Continue...</text>
            <event load="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_DELAYED" />
         </choice>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true" req = "slug">
      <text>(Slug Crew) When docking with the escort, your Slug sensed something.</text>
      <event>
         <text>You heed your Slug's advice and follow their directions to where the lifesource is, where you find a man hunched over a weapon console. Although not in as severe a condition as initially expected, but any longer and they would've most likely not made it. They sincerely thank you for saving them when you did and offer to join your crew. "I was a gunnery officer aboard our ship, consider myself somewhat of a crack shot too 'till we began running dry towards the end of our caravans journey. Now I wish to pick up where I left off and make the universe a safer place from these raiders".</text>
         <crewMember pilot="1" weapons="2" amount="1" class="human">Raynard</crewMember>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Leave.</text>
      <event />
   </choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_CREW">
   <text>The cause of the outcome of the engagement has been made clear once you boarded the vessel. It seems the escorts were still operating a few quaint Autocannons and had ran out of ammunition during the fight, likely during the last leg of their journey. Before you are able to begin salvaging, your crew spots a survivor in the weapons room hunched over a console. Although not in as severe a condition as initially expected, but any longer and they would've most likely not made it. They sincerely thank you for saving them when you did and offer to join your crew. "I was a gunnery officer aboard our ship, consider myself somewhat of a crack shot too 'till we began running dry towards the end of our caravans journey. Now I wish to pick up where I left off and make the universe a safer place from these raiders".</text>
   <crewMember pilot="1" weapons="2" amount="1" class="human">Raynard</crewMember>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Continue...</text>
      <event>
         <text>After the survivor stabilizes back on your ship, he agrees to allow you to salvage his ship as long as you help him give his former crew a proper respects and a burial at space.</text>
         <autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
         <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Take time to investigate one of the Transports.</text>
            <event load="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_DELAYED" />
         </choice>
         <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Leave.</text>
            <event />
         </choice>
      </event>
   </choice>
</event>
<event name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_BAD">
   <text>It appears that this escort had suffered from a catastrophic ammunition detonation which put a swift yet brutal end to the crew of this ship. The ships internals are warped and twisted metal frame. There is not much inside the ship to salvage and even less so on the outside.</text>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Take time to investigate one of the Transports.</text>
      <event load="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_DELAYED" />
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true" req="SCRAP_COLLECTOR">
      <text>(Scrap Recovery Arm) Attempt to recover additional salvage.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Your scrap recovery arm slowly gathers up any usable debris from the caravan wrecks drifting nearby.</text>
         <autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>(Magnetic Arm) Attempt to recover additional salvage.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Your Magnetic Arm makes quick work out of collecting the small space debris that floats around the wreckages.</text>
         <autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
      </event>
   </choice>
</event>
<event name ="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_RECON">
    <text>You repeatedly deploy your Recon Drone as it finishes investigating each ship, moving through each ones swiftly and analysing the environment on a timely manner. The Transports have mostly been sacked during the attack, however the Recon Drone's camera feed does show that the pirates have not been so thorough as initially thought, leaving behind some useful salvage.</text>
    <autoReward level="HIGH">droneparts</autoReward>
    <item_modify>
        <item type="drones" min="-5" max="-5" />
    </item_modify>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
        <text>Just as you finish salvaging the the transport, your Recon Drone on the last ship alerts you about a survivor on one of the escorts, however it would take time to finish salvaging the Transport and rescue them.</text>
        <autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Rescue the survivor.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Thanks to your Recon Drone you were able to find them just in time, and are able to stabilize their condition once aboard your ship. He states that he was a gunnery officer aboard their ship and that they were ambushed just before their final destination and were low on ammunition, unable to defend themselves. They offer their sincerest gratitude for rescuing them and offer to join your crew.</text>
					<modifyPursuit amount="1" />
					<crewMember pilot="1" weapons="2" amount="1" class="human">Raynard</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="teleporter" lvl="1">
				<text>(Teleporter) Lock on to the survivors life signature and beam them onto your ship.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Thanks to your Recon Drone you were able to find them just in time, and are able to stabilize their condition once aboard your ship. He states that he was a gunnery officer aboard their ship and that they were ambushed just before their final destination and were low on ammunition, unable to defend themselves. They offer their sincerest gratitude for rescuing them and offer to join your crew.</text>
					<crewMember pilot="1" weapons="2" amount="1" class="human">Raynard</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Leave.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You have an important mission, you have already spent enough time salvaging the transporter. You prepare to move on.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_DELAYED">
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_DELAYED_GOOD"/>
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_DELAYED_BAD"/>
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_DELAYED_AUGMENT"/>
</eventList>
<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_DELAYED_GOOD">
   <text>It looks like the pirates or who ever attacked the caravan had already taken anything it was transporting or otherwise not bolted to the floor. You salvage what you can before leaving.</text>
   <autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
   <choice hidden="true" req="SCRAP_COLLECTOR">
      <text>(Scrap Recovery Arm) Attempt to recover additional salvage.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Your scrap recovery arm slowly gathers up any usable debris from the caravan wrecks drifting nearby.</text>
         <autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true" req="MAGNET_ARM">
      <text>(Magnetic Arm) Attempt to recover additional salvage.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Your Magnetic Arm makes quick work out of collecting the small space debris that floats around the wreckages.</text>
         <autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Leave.</text>
      <event />
   </choice>
</event>
<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_DELAYED_BAD">
	<text>It looks like the pirates or who ever attacked the caravan had already taken most of the goods carried by the Transport, however they were not the most thorough, and you find a reasonable amount of salvage.</text>
   <autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Leave.</text>
      <event />
   </choice>
</event>
<event name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_TRANSPORTER_DELAYED_AUGMENT">
   <text>Who ever attacked the caravan must've missed this Transporter or mysteriously wasn't interested in ransacking it for its contents. Regardless, the crew is long dead, and there are ample supplies to help you stock yourself for your mission.</text>
   <autoReward level="RANDOM">augment</autoReward>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Leave.</text>
      <event />
   </choice>
</event>

<eventList name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_DELAYED">
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_DELAYED_GOOD"/>
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_DELAYED_BAD"/>
	<event name = "GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_DELAYED_CREW"/>
</eventList>
<event name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_DELAYED_GOOD">
   <text>The cause of the outcome of the engagement has been made clear once you boarded the vessel. It seems the escorts were still operating a few quaint Autocannons and had ran out of ammunition during the fight. Upon examining the weapon you discover, it is still in functional order, albeit dry on ammunition, and is ready to be installed!</text>
   <autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
   <weapon name="GB_CARAVAN_REWARD" />
   <choice hidden="true" req = "slug">
      <text>(Slug Crew) When docking with the escort your slug senses something.</text>
      <event>
         <text>You heed your slugs advice and follow their directions to where the lifesource is. Where you find a man hunched over a weapon console. Although not in as severe a condition as initially expected but any longer and they would've most likely not made it. They sincerely thank you for saving them when you did and offer to join your crew. "I was a gunnery officer aboard our ship, consider myself somewhat of a crack shot too 'till I we began running dry towards the end of our caravans journey. Now I wish to pick up where I left off and make the universe a safer place from these raiders".</text>
         <crewMember pilot="1" weapons="2" amount="1" class="human">Raynard</crewMember>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Leave.</text>
      <event />
   </choice>
</event>
<event name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_DELAYED_CREW">
   <text>The cause of the outcome of the engagement has been made clear once you boarded the vessel. It seems the escorts were still operating a few quaint Autocannons and had ran out of ammunition during the fight, likely during the last leg of their journey. Before you are able to begin salvaging, your crew spots a survivor in the weapons room hunched over a console. Although not in as severe a condition as initially expected, but any longer and they would've most likely not made it. They sincerely thank you for saving them when you did and offer to join your crew. "I was a gunnery officer aboard our ship, consider myself somewhat of a crack shot too 'till we began running dry towards the end of our caravans journey. Now I wish to pick up where I left off and make the universe a safer place from these raiders".</text>
   <crewMember pilot="1" weapons="2" amount="1" class="human">Raynard</crewMember>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Continue...</text>
      <event>
         <text>After the survivor stabilizes back on your ship, he agrees to allow you to salvage his ship as long as you help him give his former crew a proper respects and a burial at space.</text>
         <autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
         <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Leave.</text>
            <event />
         </choice>
      </event>
   </choice>
</event>
<event name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_ESCORT_DELAYED_BAD">
   <text>It appears that this escort had suffered from a catastrophic ammunition detonation which put a swift yet brutal end to the crew of this ship. The ships internals are warped and twisted metal frame. There is not much inside the ship to salvage and even less so on the outside.</text>
   <choice hidden="true" req="SCRAP_COLLECTOR">
      <text>(Scrap Recovery Arm) Attempt to recover additional salvage.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Your scrap recovery arm slowly gathers up any usable debris from the caravan wrecks drifting nearby.</text>
         <autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>(Magnetic Arm) Attempt to recover additional salvage.</text>
      <event>
         <text>Your Magnetic Arm makes quick work out of collecting the small space debris that floats around the wreckages.</text>
         <autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
      </event>
   </choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_CARAVAN_ABANDONED_SCAN">
	<text>Scans indicate that there is one lifeform onboard one of the better off escorts. The signal is faint but stable.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Investigate the escort and rescue them. </text>
		<event>
			<text>You head directly towards where the lifeform was detected, where you find a man hunched over a weapons console. Although not in as severe a condition as initially expected, but any longer and they would've most likely not made it. They sincerely thank you for saving them when you did and offer to join your crew. "I was a gunnery officer aboard our ship, consider myself somewhat of a crack shot too 'till we began running dry towards the end of our caravans journey. Now I wish to pick up where I left off and make the universe a safer place from these raiders".</text>
			<crewMember pilot="1" weapons="2" amount="1" class="human">Raynard</crewMember>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name = "GB_MILITIA_ESCORT">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<ship load = "SHIP_GB_MILITIA_ESCORT" hostile = "false"/>
	<text>The source of the distress beacon is emanating from a small Militia Escort. "Captain! We're very low on fuel and need some repairs desperately. Could you possibly take us to the nearest repair platform?"</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Thank you very much Captain. I'm sure we can arrange some remuneration at the shipyards.</text>
			<quest event = "GB_QUEST_MILITIA_ESCORT"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Decline.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ok, captain. We'll just, uhh, die here then."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something on board the ship.</text>
				<event load = "STORAGE_CHECK_REAL"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Attack!</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile = "true"/>
			<text>You've decided, instead of helping the Militiamen, to brutally attack them instead.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name = "GB_QUEST_MILITIA_ESCORT">
	<text>You've arrived at the shipyards, and receive a message from the Militiamen thanking you. They dispatch a shipwright to install a specialised piece of equipment on your ship.</text>
	<weapon name = "GB_CARAVAN_REWARD"/>
	<autoReward level = "MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name = "GB_FED_BOMBER_DISTRESS">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>You arrive at the beacon, only to find a Federation Bomber with its hull in tatters. Upon hailing, they explain that they had a run-in with some Mantis and are desperately low on munitions.</text>
	<ship load = "GB_SHIP_FED_BOMBER_LOWAMMO" hostile = "false"/>
	<choice hidden = "true">
		<text>Give them a small amount of ammo. [-3}]</text>
		<event>
			<text>It isn't much, but it's all you can spare. Hopefully it'll be enough to keep them alive until a supply convoy finds its way here. The crew offer a few spare droneparts to recompense.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type = "missiles" min = "-3" max = "-3"/>
				<item type="drones" min="2" max="4"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true">
		<text>Give them a medium amount of ammo. [-5}]</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Thank you, sir. This should be plenty to get us out of this hellhole." The crew dispense an augment to help you on your mission.</text>
			<autoReward level = "RANDOM">augment</autoReward>
			<item_modify>
				<item type = "missiles" min = "-5" max = "-5"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true">
		<text>Give them a large amount of ammo. [-10}]</text>
		<event>
			<text>You hand over a significant amount of ammunition to the stranded Federation soldiers. Their captain messages you: "We don't have much to give, but we could probably spare one of our weapons. The other 3 should be plenty."</text>
			<weapon name = "GB_CARAVAN_REWARD"/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type = "missiles" min = "-10" max = "-10"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true" req = "RECYCLER">
		<text>Show them your Recycler module.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"You can just... make ammo? Man, why haven't we ever got one of these? We'd be happy to buy it off you if you can spare it. We have scrap.</text>
			<choice hidden = "true">
				<text>Agree to the trade.</text>
				<event>
					<remove name = "RECYCLER"/>
					<item_modify>
						<item type = "scrap" min = "30" max = "50"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Decline.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You decide you need the Recycler more than these stranded soldiers and prepare to move on.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true" req = "CRATE_MISSILES">
		<text>Give them your ammo crate.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You hand over your ammo crate to the stranded Federation soldiers. Their captain messages you: "We don't have much to give, but we could probably spare one of our weapons. The other 3 should be plenty."</text>
			<weapon name = "GB_CARAVAN_REWARD"/>
			<remove name = "CRATE_MISSILES"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>We can't help.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"We understand. Fly safe."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something on board the ship.</text>
				<event load = "STORAGE_CHECK_REAL"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>If they're low on ammo they're an easy target, attack!</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile = "true"/>
			<text>You power up your weapons and prepare to obliterate your allies.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_FED_RESEARCH_RAIL">
   <text>A Federation research station is sending out a request on Federation encrypted channels.</text>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Contact them.</text>
      <event>
         <text>You transmit your ID to the outpost and contact them on encrypted frequencies. "Your codes are verified. Good to see you. We're a RnD facility tasked to improve the firepower of the Federation fleet and we need some field trials to be performed to work out the kinks. There's a reward in for it upon a successful egress after dispatching your target. What do you say Renegade?"</text>
         <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Agree to test the weapon.</text>
            <event>
               <text>"Excellent. We have reports of a Rebel forward scout near by for you to engage. We will send you all the supplies you need for your task. Equip the prototype Railgun and head to the designated target. Good luck!"</text>
               <quest event="GB_RAILGUN_FIELD_TEST" />
               <item_modify>
                  <item type="fuel" min="2" max="2" />
                  <item type="missiles" min="5" max="5" />
               </item_modify>
               <weapon name="GB_RAIL_1" />
            </event>
         </choice>
         <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Refuse.</text>
            <event>
               <text>"In that case farewell".</text>
               <choice hidden="true">
                  <text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
                  <event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
               </choice>
               <choice hidden="true">
                  <text>Do nothing.</text>
                  <event />
               </choice>
            </event>
         </choice>
      </event>
   </choice>
   <choice hidden="true">
      <text>Ignore the station.</text>
      <event>
         <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Continue...</text>
            <event>
               <text>You aren't interested in the station. You ignore them.</text>
               <choice hidden="true">
                  <text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
                  <event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
               </choice>
               <choice hidden="true">
                  <text>Do nothing.</text>
                  <event />
               </choice>
            </event>
         </choice>
      </event>
   </choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_TESTING_RAILGUN" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_REBEL_FIGHT">
	<destroyed load="GB_RAIL_TEST_DESTROYED_REBEL"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEAD_CREW_REBEL"/>
	<triggeredEvent event="GB_RAIL_TEST_REBEL_ESCAPE" time="60" thisFight="true" clearOnJump="true">
		<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_TIMER" pos="default">
			<warning time="10.0" flash="true"/>
			<tooltip>The Rebel will escape as soon as this timer runs out.</tooltip>
		</triggeredEventBox>
		<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
</ship>

<event name = "GB_RAILGUN_FIELD_TEST">
	<text>This is where the station reported rebel activity, and sure enough, a scout comes in to intercept you almost immediately. Time to show them who's boss.</text>
	<ship load = "SHIP_TESTING_RAILGUN" hostile = "true"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load = "COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name = "GB_RAIL_TEST_DESTROYED_REBEL">
	<text>The rebel ship has been eliminated, thanks to the prototype tech. You scrap the ship.</text>
	<autoReward level = "HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="GB_RAIL_TEST_REBEL_ESCAPE">
	<text>The rebels jump away, and you sense you lost valuable time on the fleet.</text>
	<instantEscape/>
	<modifyPursuit amount = "1"/>
	<choice hidden = "true" req = "GB_RAIL_1" lvl="1">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The commander of the station is unimpressed, and takes the prototype weapon away with him.</text>
			<remove name = "GB_RAIL_1"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true" req = "GB_RAIL_1" lvl="0">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name = "GB_MUSEUM_TOUR">  <!--I guess I'm trying to evoke Trantor here-->
	<text>This planet hosts a large human settlement, covering a large portion of the surface. The landscape is covered in sprawling urban landscapes cradled between towering peaks on the supercontinent. Standing tall amid the city is a grand building, surrounded by fountains and seemingly the centre of attention.</text>
	<choice hidden = "true">
		<text>Land and look around the building.</text>
		<event><!--Can I can I use grizzled here?-->
			<text>A grizzled Federation officer is guarding the front of the complex, allowing select members of the public to pass through into the halls beyond. You and your crew approach, and, recognising your uniforms, the officer stands aside to let you pass.</text>
			<choice hidden = "true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>You enter into the atrium, where you see many great displays of equipment of various points of the Federation's timespan in this Universe. Some things depicted here, especially the events do not line up perfectly with what you are familiar with in your universe. You aren't sure if that's due to errors of the displays or a divergence in the timeline between this and your universe. Entering the main corridor, you realise that this is a museum, built to contain old Federation memorabilia. A curator scuttles up to you, and, seeing your insignia, asks if they can provide anything to assist with your mission - for a price.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Take a tour around the museum.</text>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Let's get straight to business, shall we?</text>
						<event load = "GB_MUSEUM_PURCHASE_DONATE"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the city.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Whilst it might be quite the sight, you don't have time to waste on tourism.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name = "GB_MUSEUM_PURCHASE_DONATE">
	<text>The curator bows obsequiously, and takes you into a storeroom, where a variety of antique weapons are hanging on the walls, neatly categorised by year and users. You note that the 'Federation' section is rather empty. "I, sir, would be delighted to assist you in any way. Well, any way that helps us both.</text> 
	<choice hidden = "true">
		<text>Purchase an old Federation weapon.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"An Autocannon, sir? Cheap, and hastily assembled, yet excellent at suppressing shields? A fine choice."</text>
			<weapon name = "GB_SHOP_ITEM_WEAPONS_CANNONS_OLD"/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-10" max="-35"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true">
		<text>Purchase an old Separatist weapon.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"A Coilgun, sir? A weapon for the patient. Good taste, they're fine weapons."</text>
			<weapon name = "GB_COILGUNS"/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-30" max="-45"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true">
		<text>Purchase an old Harmony weapon.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"A Gauss rifle, sir? Of course, of course. An acquired taste, for certain, but deadly in the right hands."</text>
			<weapon name = "GB_GAUSS"/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-30" max="-45"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true" req = "LIST_CREW_FEDERATION_ELITE">
		<text>(Elite Crew) Do you have anything... newer?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Well, funny you should ask that, sir. We do keep some more... experimental armaments in our back rooms."</text>
			<weapon name = "GB_RAIL"/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-40" max="-55"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true" req="GB_AC_1">
		<text>Donate your autocannon to the museum.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hmm. A mark one autocannon. Quite a poor specimen, as well." They grumble a little, but eventually you talk them into paying you for it.</text>
			<autoReward level = "MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true" req="GB_AC_2">
		<text>Donate your autocannon to the museum.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The curator starts when you offer your donation. "A mark two? In excellent condition, as well. I would be honoured to take this off your hands, captain."</text>
			<autoReward level = "HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden = "true" req="GB_AC_3">
		<text>Donate your autocannon to the museum.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh my, oh my! A mark three. Gosh, I haven't seen one of these for... oh, must be twenty years. A little beat-up I see, but this would be a prize addition to our collection here." They offer you as much scrap as they can find in their vaults.</text>
			<autoReward level = "HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
			<choice hidden = "true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>The museum drop off even more scrap as you leave the building.</text>
					<autoReward level = "HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--<choice req="GB_AC_4">
		<text>Donate your autocannon to the museum.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>-->
</event>

</FTL>